1. openBrowser(URL)
5. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
9. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
13. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-account"), "agungpriyadi")
17. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Password"), "Laskar123456")
21. click(findTestObject("Login/btn-sign in"))
25. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
29. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/verify-succes-acount-login"))
33. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/icon-search"))
37. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"))
41. sendKeys(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), Keys.chord("IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD", ENTER))
45. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/verify-product-iphone-12 -pro"))
49. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/btn-product - IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD"))
53. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/button_Add to Cart"))
57. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"), 7)
61. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"))
65. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/btn_checkout"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
69. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/btn_checkout"))
73. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Online Payment - WeChat"))
77. check(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkbox__I accept"))
81. click(findTestObject("Checkout/button_Checkout_Payment"))
85. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Checkout/iframe_payment_online"), 10)
89. click(findTestObject("Checkout/iframe_payment_online"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
93. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Checkout/button_Approve"), 10)
97. click(findTestObject("Checkout/button_Approve"))
101. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Checkout/button_Continue shopping"), 10)
105. click(findTestObject("Checkout/button_Continue shopping"))
109. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/track your order"), 0)
113. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/track your order"))
117. click(findTestObject("Checkout/button_Order Details"))
121. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/verify-order list"), 7)
125. takeScreenshot()
129. closeBrowser()